{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Concrete Driveway \u0026 Floor Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/40015/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40015,"taskName":"Concrete Driveways \u0026 Floors - Install","taskDescription":"Install Concrete Driveways \u0026 Floors","xmTaskDescriptor":"Concrete Driveway \u0026 Floor Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":61,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"concrete driveway floor patio walkway","textMessagingName":"Inst Concrete Flat","rolloverLongDesc":"Used for driveways \u0026 floors. Does not require extensive vertical forms. Appropriate when building or replacing old mostly flat concrete structures.","rolloverShortDesc":"Build forms, pour concrete, finish flat concrete","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install Concrete Floors and Driveways. HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated concrete floor contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Concrete Driveway Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Concrete Floor \u0026 Flatwork Installers","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":16,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Concrete Driveways \u0026 Floors - Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Concrete Driveways \u0026 Floors - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Concrete Project","urlName":"Concrete-Flatwork-for-Driveways-Floors-etc-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Concrete Driveway \u0026 Floor Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"concrete,driveway,patio,walkway,sidewalk","emcCategoryOid":-12015,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":339,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40015/":{"taskOID":40015,"originalTaskOID":40015,"setID":339,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4055,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Surface","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which concrete surfaces do you want to have installed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2093,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Driveway/parking area","answerDisplayText":"Driveway/parking area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":963,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Basement floor","answerDisplayText":"Basement floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2720,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Garage floor","answerDisplayText":"Garage floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4536,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Pad for a light structure","answerDisplayText":"Pad for a light structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10465,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Interior floor","answerDisplayText":"Interior floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502853,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of concrete driveway or floor project is this? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"Type of Project","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5289,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replacement of existing concrete","answerDisplayText":"Replacement of existing concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4139,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"New concrete for existing home","answerDisplayText":"New concrete for existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4146,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"New construction of home","answerDisplayText":"New construction of home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4055,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Surface","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which concrete surfaces do you want to have installed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2093,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Driveway/parking area","answerDisplayText":"Driveway/parking area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":963,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Basement floor","answerDisplayText":"Basement floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2720,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Garage floor","answerDisplayText":"Garage floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4536,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Pad for a light structure","answerDisplayText":"Pad for a light structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10465,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Interior floor","answerDisplayText":"Interior floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2093,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Driveway/parking area","answerDisplayText":"Driveway/parking area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":963,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Basement floor","answerDisplayText":"Basement floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2720,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Garage floor","answerDisplayText":"Garage floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4536,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Pad for a light structure","answerDisplayText":"Pad for a light structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10465,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Interior floor","answerDisplayText":"Interior floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502853,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of concrete driveway or floor project is this? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"Type of Project","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5289,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replacement of existing concrete","answerDisplayText":"Replacement of existing concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4139,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"New concrete for existing home","answerDisplayText":"New concrete for existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4146,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"New construction of home","answerDisplayText":"New construction of home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5289,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replacement of existing concrete","answerDisplayText":"Replacement of existing concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4139,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"New concrete for existing home","answerDisplayText":"New concrete for existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4146,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"New construction of home","answerDisplayText":"New construction of home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isCookielessUser":true}